Guide to the Ipas Records, 1965-2020; 1965-ongoing RL.00617
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Asia Programs, 1985-2012; 23 boxes
  - Vietnam Programs, 1988-2010
    - Donor proposal 01, team retreat 01, donor report 01, RHP donor report 01, RHP appraisal 01, midwives workshop 01, service provider research study and presentation 01, needs assessment 01, reports 01, trip reports 01, RHP report 01, Dr. Loan presentation 01, WHO MA protocols 01, national RH strategy 01, demog info 01, marketing 01, results framework 01, CAC monitoring 91, reports 01, team mtgs 01-02, RHP general 01-02, donors comms 01-03, CAC WHO proposal 01-03, CAC monitoring 01-03, RHP mtgs 01-04, Comms 01-03, Admin misc 01-04, master plan 01-10, RHP planning and proposal 02, donor trip report 02, donor reports 02, trip reports 02, midlevel providers conf in SA 02, presentations 02, strategies 02, reports 02, WHO report 02, standards and guidelines 02, MOH 02, RHP training eval 02, instrument processing 02, CAC baseline 02, CAC donor reports 02, CAC monitoring 02, CAC manual 02, CAC partners mtgd 02-03, CAC donor report 02-03, PACCOM report 02-03, WHO CAC reports 02-03, RHP TA and workplan 02-03, Gender/adol/RH workshop 02-03, Pathfinder med educ proj 02-04, strategies 02-05, 2001-2002 (Box 101)
    - CAC planning/corresp 03, CAC training 03, Adol Working Group 03, MVA video 03, stats 03, meetings 03, Gender TOT 03, donor report 03, RHP donor report 03, RHP report to Dutch 03, T&L reports 03, RHP youth proposal 03, longrange planning 03, program reviews 03, MOH bid 03, lease contract 03, license 03, numbers tracked 03, de Bruyn consultancy to RHP 03, Gender/adol/RH TOT 03, adol report 03, MA study/report 03, trip reports 03-05, RHP planning 03-04, EZ grip trial 03-04, PACCOM 03-04, CAC donor report 03, CAC donor proposal/corres 03-06, donor report 04, CAC planning/corres 04, Safe motherhood 04, planning forms 04, CAC report 04, dissemination 04, RHP proposal to dutch 04-06, CAC planning 04-06, CAC proposal 04-07, CAC project doc 04-07, med school safe AB project 05, workplans 05, Smart Women Clubs 05, partners mtg 05, intern 05, meetings 05, TSDI 05, Labeuf fellowship 05, CAC donor report 05, RHP donor report 05, CAC evals 05-06, data 05-06, CAC 06, RHP history and workplan 06, planning 06, activities 06, donor report 06, performance improvements 06, RHP presentation 06, Edelman consultancy 06, misc 06, donor report 06, scale up and e-learning 06, 2003-2006 (Box 102)
    - Background/RH reports 93-99 (two folders); misc articles 94-99; UNICEF 96-99; PAFP 96-99; training report 97; USAID – HIV/AIDS 97-00; WHO 97-00; anthro study/abortion 98; abortion assessment 98; contraception 98-99; NGO resource ctr 98-00; background/RH reports 98-01 (two folders); UNFPA 98-01; focus groups MVA 99; other NGOs 99; FCI 99; gender & RH 99-001; World Bank 99-01; Pop council 99-01; market assessment 00-01; 2nd tri 00-01; CAC Project 01-03, 1993-2001 (Box 163)
    - SWOT 02; Ipas country report 02; report for midlevel provider conf 02; pubs 04-07; pubs in Vietnamese 04-07; CAC Phase 3 proposal 04-07; Ipas program summaries 04-10; training numbers 06; MA training report 06; CAC project eval 06; donor reports/presentations 06-07; director workplan 06; dissemination 06-08; pilot report 07; MOH contracts 07; trip reports 07; donor mtg 07; MVA Plus study 07; data 07; CAC eval 07; CAC needs assessment 07; donor concept paper 07; TA to RHPs 07; RHP bulletin 07-08; Ipas programs 07-08; strat plan 07-09; MOH CAC scale-up 07-10; planning 08; trip report 08; trainee follow-up 08; board bullets 08; plan-it reports 08; MA – SIDA global 08; CAC training reports 08; MA 08; CAC eval medical ctr 08; CAC training review 08; advocacy workshop 09; MA report 09; closure notes 09; M&E closure results 09; audit minutes 09; Medabon 09; Ipas program summary 09; MA community-based activity report 09; Do Thi Hong Nga 10; background 10; AB in VN book chapter 10; Eval of RHP 10, 2002-2010 (Box 164)
  - Cambodia Programs, 1997-2010
    - Laws 97-06; Background 01-04; Articles and Pubs 02-07; Presentations 03-07; articles/reports 03-09; Project Chrono 03-09; correspondence 03-10; trip reports 04-08; magnitude study contract 05; contracts 05, 1997-2005 (Box 157)
    - DFID/RMMP proposals 06; DFID procurement 06; RMMP tech proposal 06; RMMP project memo 06; RMMP TOR 06; RMMP bids/subcontracts/MOU 06; RMMP background 06-07; consultants 06-07; tools and indicators 06-07; mtg notes 06-07; MVA supplies and dist 06-08; contact info 06-09; RMMP corresp 06-09; programs 06-08; National RH programme 07; Eval training courses MCH ctr 07; RMMP inception phase 07; training plan sources 07; mag study dissemination workshop 07; MCH KAP survey 07; press release 07; RMMP presentations 07; needs assessment placard 07; Options subcontract 07-10; trip reports 07-10; CMA strat plan 07-10; CMA contracts 08; Options 07-10; RMMP Options trip reports 08; PAA workshop 08; CMA summary report 08; DTC ads 08; CMA corresp 08; CMA non-contract fund requests 08; CMA 08; CAC training 08; RMMP roadmap and deliverables 08; corresp 08; board bullets 08; RMMP 08; local orgs 08; RMMP logframe 08; trip report 08; training recs 08; RMMP monthly reports 08-09; GEM data 08-09; RMMP bi-annual reports 08-09; WCG sales and distr 08-10; RMMP site assessment tools 09; 2nd tri training 09; 2nd tri training data 09; 2nd tri VCAT report 09; Anon2 corresp/notes 09; planning 09; RMMP 2 09; Options proposal 09; Anon2 organogram and roles/respons 09; RMMP Options/DFID monthly reports 09-10; planning and budgeting 09-10; program/results summary 10; GEM data 10; MA 10; revised budget 10; RMMP Phase II study 10; strat planning 10; MA training 10; Phase II research study 10 RMMP report summary 10, 2006-2010 (Box 158)
  - Pakistan Programs, 2003-2010
    - NCMNH newsletters 03-06; background 06; org effectiveness 06; MSS earthquake 06; facility logbook 06; NCMNH info pack 06; trip reports 06-07; background 06-10 (4 folders); DFID 07; stakeholders mtg 07; MA 07; presentations 07; FIGO 07; RWD 07; NCMNH contract 07; corresp 07; AAHUNG 07; NCMNH training letters 07; NCMNH 2nd women's RH mtg 07; MOH donor mtg 07; workplan 07; PAC Sindh mtg 07; SAFOG 07; SAFOG presentations 07; SAFOG evals 07; M Luke visit 07; NCNMH revision 07-08; Misc 07-09; donor corresp 07-09; AAHUNG 07-09, 2003-2007 (Box 161)
    - Training in Nepal 08; planning 08; NCMNH training 08; PAC clinical training 08; Ipas in PK 08; AAHUNG materials 08; donor proposal 08; workplan 08; donor update 08; NCMNH reports 08; PRB engage 08; GEM 08; GEM orientation 08; monthly stats 08; SOGP/FIGO situation analysis 08-09; reports/pubs 08-09; background 08-10; MVA 08-10; donor report MAP 08-10; donor report pilot 08-10; donor proposals 08-12; strat PAC alliance 09; ED 09; DFID bid 09; NCMNH contract 09; NCMNH/Ipas 09; AAHUNG project eval 09; PRSP 09; Ipas PK overview 09; EST/VCAT workshop 09; planning 09; NCMNH contract 09-10; WCG contract 10; PPD consultant trainings 10; Aman VCAT 10; indicators 10; VCAT corresp 10; VCAT logistics 10; gender/health/rights workshops 10; small grants contracts 10; background 10; ToO 10; program/summary results 10; GEM 10-11; NCMNH service agreement 10-11, 2008-2010 (Box 162)
  - Asia Regional, 1997-2011
    - Afghanistan refugee proposal 02; Bangladesh MR training 87-98, MR Coordinating Comm 90-93, BAPSA 90-95, Women's Health Coalition 90-95, Mohammadpur Fertility Services 90-95, SIDA 91-97, Assoc. for Comm and Pop Research 93, Infection prevention report 93, FP and MCH logistics reports 94, program review 95, program report 96, PRIME proposal 98, misc 99, SIDS MR report 04, SRH report 05; Cambodia HS pilot project 01, trip report 04, UNFPA RH sub program 05, Health sector support program 05, USAID PAC 05, User fees background study, NRHP KAP study 05, AB estimates 05, data 05-06, background 05-06, planning 05-06, research brief 06, midwifery forum report 06, needs assessment 06; China background 98-00, Ipas White Paper 99, overview for board 01; Indonesia 06, Japan JOICFP 75, background 97-98, trip reports 97-98, donor strategies 98; Korea 73-78; Malaysia 00; Mongolia 00; Pakistan 01; Papua New Guinea 94; Philippines 02; Thailand 05-06; Turkey program development and planning 86-87, trip reports 86-92, Misc 88-90, contracts 90-92, Financioglu 90-92, Eval 90-91, field reports 90-92, proposal/reports 91-92, comms 91-94 (Box 103)
    - Strategic planning 01, presentations 01, strat planning results 02, sales analysis 01, teams roles 02, Safe Motherhood 02, development lessons learned 02, team mtgs 02, WHO/SEARO RH mtg 03, restructuring 03, CTL meeting 03, marketing 04, MVA launch plans 04-05, general corresp 04-06, regional planning 05, MAP 05-06, Board presentation 06, strategy and decision tree 06, expand impact 06, APCRSH planning 06, planning 06, trainers workshop 06, MVA 06, partnerships 06, team mtgs 06, trip reports 06, 2001-2006 (Box 104)
    - Bangladesh background 99-00; China background 00; china consultant contract 00; China white paper 00; RH resources 00-01; NGO Networks for Health 01; CDQ PRIME 03; Bangladesh background 03-06; USAID guidelines 03-04; Thailand 04; APCSRH 04; JHPIEGO Bangkok conf 04; SAFOG 05; WHO workshop 05; strat visioning process 05; IPPF M&E workshop 05; DFID strategy 05; Advocacy Task Force 05-06; misc corresp 05-08; trip reports 06; APCRSH 06; indicators/stats 06-09; Bangladesh program/corresp 06-09; country summaries 06-09; Indonesia 06-09; partnerships 07; FIGO 07; APCRSH 07; PNMCH 07; knowledge mngmnt 07; Meetings 07; Access 07; RH supplies Coalition 07; ICMA 07; SAFOG pre-conf workshop 07; MAP/PPDA 07; Indonesia 07; AOFOG 07; regional workshop 07; M&E pilot project 07; trip reports 07; Philippines 07; training global initiative 07; training analysis 07; sustainable supply 07, 1999-2007 (Box 167)
    - WHO 07; Asia TOT 07; APCRSH 07; M&E global indicators 07; experts mtg 07; M&E pilot 07; regional directors exchange 07-08; M&E 07-08; Malaysia 07-08; AOFOG 07-08; Monthly update mtgs 07-08; program planning 07-09; Islam 07-09; N Shamsuddin 07-09; OE 07-09; MVA 07-09; MSI 07-09; R&E global mtg 08; FIGO 08; ICMA 08; RWD 08; 2nd tri 08; results data 08; TIPS 08; program/PPD 08; global directors' mtg 08; board mtg 08; PPD orientation 08; programs unit 08; comms 08; GEM orientation 08; QA 08; program planning 08; Maguire/Luke trip 08; regional directors mtgs 06-08; ICMA info 08; global pilot findings/recs 08; sustainability workshop 08; M&E reports/updates 08; PPD 08; training workshop report 08; MVA champion workshop 08; advocacy workshop 08; C Weg consultant 08; results areas & planning 08; planning 08; background Bangladesh 08; Ipas in Asia 08; background East Timor 08; background Asia Regional 07-08: WHO 07; Asia TOT 07; APCRSH 07; M&E global indicators 07; experts mtg 07; M&E pilot 07; regional directors exchange 07-08; M&E 07-08; Malaysia 07-08; AOFOG 07-08; Monthly update mtgs 07-08; program planning 07-09; Islam 07-09; N Shamsuddin 07-09; OE 07-09; MVA 07-09; MSI 07-09; R&E global mtg 08; FIGO 08; ICMA 08; RWD 08; 2nd tri 08; results data 08; TIPS 08; program/PPD 08; global directors' mtg 08; board mtg 08; PPD orientation 08; programs unit 08; comms 08; GEM orientation 08; QA 08; program planning 08; Maguire/Luke trip 08; regional directors mtgs 06-08; ICMA info 08; global pilot findings/recs 08; sustainability workshop 08; M&E reports/updates 08; PPD 08; training workshop report 08; MVA champion workshop 08; advocacy workshop 08; C Weg consultant 08; results areas & planning 08; planning 08; background Bangladesh 08; Ipas in Asia 08; background East Timor 08; background Afghanistan 08; background Indonesia 08; Anon2 regional workplan 08; savings workshop 08; MA 08, 2007-2008 (Box 168)
    - FIGO 08-09; R&E forms/info 08-09; pubs/background 08-09; GTN 08-09; ASAP 08-09; MA 08-09; Bangladesh background 08-10; Meetings 08-10; planning 09; DFID 09; strat planning 09; IPPF workshop 09; SOPs 09; youth strategy 09; Plan-it 09; 2nd tri 09; adverse events 09; IPPF-SARO 09; clinical affairs 09; RWD indicators 09; USAID 09; trip reports 09; Bangladesh trip reports 09; 2nd tri training 09; best practices mtg 09; global policy 09; TSDI global mtg 09; VCAT workshop 09; trainee F-U updates 09; TSDI corresp 09; Data solutions working group 09; consultant packet 09; regional planning 09; IPPF-SARO contract 09; MA resources 09; final activities/budget 09; IPPF training 09-10; GEM 09-10; East Timor 09-10, 2008-2009 (Box 169)
    - PMDUP tender 10; FIGO 10; regional planning 10; strat planning 10; recruitment 10; job descriptions 10; TSDI 10; DFID regional grant 10; Bangladesh 10; TSDI training docs 10; SIDA global grant 10; strat planning 10; DFID tender 10; background 10; IWC 10; VCAT Thailand budget 10; VCAT Thailand planning 10; First Asian Congress 10; IPPF/SARO mats 10; IPPF/SARO reports 10; Anon15 proposal 10; IPPF/SARO corresp 10; VCAT Thailand parts; VCAT Thailand corresp 10; VCAT TOT general 10; SIDA 10; strat planning directors mtg 10; corresp 10; trainers contracts 10; IPPF/SARO workshop parts 10; Bangladesh RHP working paper 10; photo – CD meeting 10; violence mats 10; JSi sustainability supply 10; GEM 10; MVA supply 10; ASAP 10; fragile states DFID 10-11, 2010 (Box 170)
- Africa Programs, 1973-2012; 23 boxes
  Ipas's first Africa programs involved establishment of clinics for treatment of women's complications resulting from incomplete abortion and provision of contraceptives in Ghana in 1981. In 1983, Ipas sponsored demonstration training projects in Nigeria in MVA technique for treating complications resulting from incomplete abortion. Hospital-based MVA training projects followed in Nigeria, Zaire, Zambia, Kenya in the late 1980s, and research projects commenced in the early 1990s in Zimbabwe and Kenya. Starting in the mid-1990s, Ipas programs in Africa expanded dramatically, due to donor grants dedicated to organizational efforts in east and southern Africa, along with growth in overall organizational capacity in policy/advocacy and marketing. In 2000, Ipas established the Africa Alliance for Reproductive Health and Rights to coordinate and support country- and region-wide activities and extend programming to countries where Ipas did not have a country office. By 2000, Ipas had in-country offices in Nigeria, Ethiopia, Uganda, Ghana and South Africa, and a regional office in Kenya for the Ipas Africa Alliance. Ipas sold MVA instruments throughout the entire continent during this time period.
  Areas of highest impact and results in the Africa region by Ipas include: assisting governments in national scale-up of postabortion care initiatives to improve quality of and access to treatment of abortion complications; conducting health systems and cost research studies on services; developing quality of care and instructional tools for improving postabortion care services and preventing repeat abortion via postabortion family planning; establishing comprehensive abortion care services in countries where laws were supportive; creating national standards and guidelines for best practices in comprehensive abortion care; advocating for reform to expand legal indications for abortion services; documenting coverage and utilization models in safe abortion care; provision of postabortion care services by mid-level and primary care providers; provision of reproductive health services for special needs populations, such as refugees, adolescents and people with HIV/AIDS; and advancement of women's sexual and reproductive rights as part of human rights.
  Ipas's Africa programs were under the direction of various staff during this time period - most notably Ann Leonard (Program Officer in the late 1980s), followed by Harrison McKay (Director of Programs), Joan Healy (Director of Programs in the 1990s), Jennifer Potts (Africa Desk Director, or regional director) and Khama Rogo (Vice President for Africa and VP for Medical Affairs) in the late 1990s, Eunice Brookman-Amissah (Vice President for Africa and Director of Ipas Africa Alliance) starting in 2000, Uche Ekenna as Africa Desk Director starting in 2003, William Sampson (Africa Regional Director) starting in 2008, and split in 2011 between William Sampson as Director of West and South Africa Programs and Igbal Hossain as Director of East Africa Programs.
  - Nigeria Programs, 1984-2003
    - FEMOPE marketing 85-96; Dr. Bamgbose 86-88; Lagos project correspondence 86-92; Zaria correspondence 87-88; programs overview 87-91; correspondence 87-98; Tubi reports 88; Port Harcourt 88-91; background 88-96; equipment 90-93; Zaria 89; market research 89-90; Tubi correspondence 89-90; research 89-91; Zaria 90-91; Lagos reports 90-95; HAAL 90-97; Tubi correspondence 91-92; Nigeria IV project working files 91-92; Prof Ojo correspondence 91-94; Zaria 91-94; FMOH/PAFA 91-95; PATH collaboration 91-95, 1985-1996 (Box 41)
    - Misc correspondence 92-93; Ayo Tubi reports 92-95; Lagos project correspondence 92-95; donor proposals/reports/correspondence 92-96; Ayo Tubo correspondence 92-95; private MD trainings 92-96; Nigeria V working files 93-94; Expanding Access project working files 93-96; ADB project 94; Zaria reports/proposals 94-96; Dr. Shittu 94-96; reports 94-97; Laniyan consultant 95; IFH report to ODA 95; LSS curriculum 95; Lagos correspondence 95-96; NYSC training 95-96; NARD training 95-96; NMA 95-96; Ayo Tubi correspondence 95-96; Tubi reports 95-96; MOH project 95-96; NGO collaboration 96-97; CHAN working files 95-97, 1992-1997 (Box 42)
    - Country summaries 96-99; trip reports 96-97; CHAN project working files 96-99; REACH tracking 97-98; SMT background 97; field reports 97; strat planning workshop 97; articles 97-99; donor proposals/report 97-99; SMT 97-00; PACNET meetings 97-01; SMT meetings 97-01; strategic plan 98; papers 98; background 98-99; SMT mailings 98-99; field reports 98-99; comms 98-03; chief 99; AGHA 99; Ayo Tubo correspondence 99; planning 99; policy 99, 1996-1999 (Box 43)
    - Reports 00; meetings 00; plan/proposal/strategy 00; history 00; SOGON 00; PAC to scale workshop 00; correspondence 00; NGO constitution 00 ;women's health organization 00; LRRDC 00; EMPARC 00; IFH 00; SMT correspondence 00-01; Tubi correspondence 00-01; PRIME 00-01; Pathfinder 00-01; IFH 00-01; correspondence 00-03; donor proposals/reports/correspondence 00-04; small grants 01; SOGON/NMA/WONCA 01; ARFH 01; CAUP 01; NAMMN 01; trip reports 01; INTRAH 01; planning 02; MVA plus launch 02-04; research projects 03; registration and lease 03 proposal/correspondence 98; donor reports 98; DFID Year one working files 99; country summary 99; marketing 99; DFID year 2 00; contracts 00; reports 00-01; team meetings 00; DFID year 3 01; Goldman Judin 01-02; proposals 01-02, 2000-2002 (Box 44)
  - Ethiopia Programs, 1988-2004
    - Background 88-93; comms 91-93; Ethiopia II donor proposal/reports 92-96; history of programs 92-99; background 93-98; MOH agreements 95-96; Ethiopia II working files 94-95; working files 96-97; correspondence and reports 96-97; proposals 96-98; talks/papers 96-99; background 98-99; reports 98-00; donor proposals/reports 98-01; correspondence 98-01; ESOG 99-00; NGO registration 00; small grants 99-00; RH mtg 00; TOTs 00; workplan/logframe 00-01; team minutes 00-01; trip reports 00-02; small grants 00-02; donor reports 00-03; progress reports 00-03; donor proposals/correspondence 5 year project 00-03; country 00-04, 1988-2004 (Box 49)
    - Consultants 01, legal reform 01, monthly reports 01; office lease 01-02; workplans 01-02; small grants program 01-02; Saba visit 02; Hailu orientation 02; HAPSCO presentation 02; CPRHA curriculum 02; management/monitoring 01-03; BOD presentation 02; 63iii 02; pre-service curriculum 02-03; RAMOS proposal 03; program overview/planning 03; Finland proposal 03; internal report 03; AWG 03; small grants 03; donor report 03-04; planning 04; management/monitoring 04; Netherlands contract 04; donor workplan year 4 04-05, 2001-2005 (Box 50)
  - South Africa Programs, 1994-2010
    - Women's health projects 94-00; DFID history 95-99; new ideas 95-97; correspondence 95-01; ODA project 96-98; RRA Alliance 96-00; curriculum 97; midwives, 1994-2001 (Box 45)
    - ODA FY 97; Abortion care manual 98; South Africa Office & Registration 01-06; Art of Assoc 02; TOP Hearings Report 02; CHSRD Subcontract 03; Registration of South Africa Office 03; Contracts: FY03; Proposal GHC Congressional Study Tour FY06; Articles/Publications FY06; Eddie Mhlanga 06; Planning/P&R FY06 PET FY06; 11th World Congress on Public Health 2006 (Abstract); Atlantic Philanthropies Concept Paper FY06; Youth Centres Report FY06; MVA Access Questions 2006; Press Release FY06; MOUs-DOH and Capetown Univ FY06; Donor Proposal/Report FY06; NWP Youth Project 06-08; Youth Centres Proposal 06-08; Leases 06-09; Tshireletso FY07; National Department of Health Grant to RSA Ipas FY07; Umtapo Centre FY07; Youth Centre Proposal 07; KZN Networks 07-08; Masimanyane FY 07-08; Masisukemini Project 07-08; 3 Year Plans 07-09; Mosaic Project 07-09; Best Practices Meeting South Africa 11/08; Budgeting 08; 2nd Tri Project 08; Program Planning & Budgeting FY 08; Planning 08; AnCRA Project Report FY08-09; Team Mtg FY09; Ga-Rankuwa & Stinkwater townships FY09; Consultant & Staff Contracts 09-10; Donor Proposals/Reports FY09-10, 1997-2010 (Box 180)
  - Kenya Programs, 1986-2005
    - Trip reports 87-92; correspondence 86-88; Kenya II proposal/contracts 88-90; correspondence 89-91; donor correspondence 94; reports 94-95; background 95-99; country summaries 95-99; Clinical Officers project working files 96-97; REACH numbers 96-98; Nairobi office 97-01; FCI 97; Kenya OR (operations research) working files 95-98; National Expansion working files 96-98; Sida projects 97, 1987-1998 (Box 46)
    - OR dissemination 98; background 98-00; refugee project working files 98-99; PRIME I working files 98-00; Khama Rogo 99; Sida proposal and contracts 99-01; Kenya donor proposals 99-00, 1998-2000 (Box 47)
    - ICR handover 00; PAC scale-up mtg 00; CHAK 00; Orero 00; COBAC paper 00; PRIME I dissemination 00; PRIME II working files 00-02; Women's Health Project 00; WHO safe ab mtg 00; Pathfinder USAID project proposal/working files 00-01; correspondence 00-01; Ipas/FIDA/KMA proposal 00-01; minutes 00-01; WHO midwifery module 00-01; reports 00-02; trip reports 00-03; strategic plan 01-05; Sida/AVSC proposal/planning 01; Sida reports 01; Teen Web survey proposal 01; RHAP project 01; small grants proposal 01-02; K2 launch 01-03; planning 02; donor profiles 02; research data 02-03; TeenWeb project and dissemination 02-03; hand-off to Alliance 03; planning 03, 2000-2005 (Box 48)
  - Ghana Programs, 1992-2010
    - Proposals 92; clinic project 82-83; equipment 88-97; correspondence 88-97; background/project development 89-95; field proposals/reports 89-96; Kumasi/KATH correspondence 9-94; Korle Bu correspondence 91-96; trip reports 91-93; planning materials 92-95; donor proposals/reports; 93-96; contracts 94; trip reports 94-95; Safe Motherhood 94-96; Brookman Amissah ICR contract/reports 94-96; Ghana II working files 94-95; ICR correspondence 94-96; PRIME 96; Taylor 96-97; working files 96-97; mothercare 96-98; trip reports 96-99; country summary 97-98; workplan 99-00; Taylor at SA conference 99; PRIME 99-00; strategy mtg 00; strategy plan 01-05; Ab care services mtg 04, 1992-2004 (Box 51)